Hello hello everyone our topic today is
about the comparison of DSC Ergo and ICICI Lombard's Super Top Lung. Today we will give you all the information about these two
in retail comparison.
Subscribe to that. According to that,
Super Top Lung is a good option for everyone and it is very important to have it
in increasing our weight because it
provides a lot and both of them are
very good for this problem. First of all let us
talk about the company's name and
secondly let us talk about the basic details of the company.
HDFC Ergo is a joint
venture between HDFC Bank and ICICI Bank
International, a German company. It has a large one percent
stake and it is a major insurance
company in the private sector. It is a major
insurance company in the motor sector
and a major travel company. It was formed
in 2012 and if we talk about it in Mumbai, then
it is the largest insurance company in the private sector in the market.
It was formed in 2012
and the joint venture is
with Jhalawar which is a joint venture of Toronto's
best insurance company ICICI.  6 per
cent stake and subscribe quarter in
Mumbai, both the companies
are very good in themselves and talk about claim settlement ratio,
both the companies have a very good product,
first of all let's talk about deductible but it is not what
you have to
decide and after that amount
your top up works, this is
not available in Aisi Ramban 3 lakh and 5 lakh, when
in school if we talk about the range of 2 lakh 45 lakh association, then
in Embassy the maximum
coverage up to 20 lakh
is available, whereas in Aisi Budam 5 lakh to 50
lakh hospitalization and post
hospitalization Shyam, if we
talk about the policy period of both the companies, then in Embassy
it is available for 2 years and in this if you
subscribe for 2 years then you
get a discount of 5 per cent tax, when in Aisi Budam
this subscription is available, if you
take a policy for three years in Aisi Budam then if we
talk about the family floater then the
maximum number of members who have set the policy is
tattoo and two children, whereas in ICICI
In Lombard, policy is available for two door three channel.
Existing disease means
if the policy holder has
any disease before taking the policy, then it covers him after two years
and if we talk about subscribed panel hospital, then it
is ABS and
benefits with these 5,000 hospitals, this means
that whichever MS Word you have selected,
if it is used, then it
is set with this number, same for example, if you
subscribe to
Rs 123 lakh and ICICI Lombard, there is a
condition that it will
not be applicable for West Indies, this
feature is not available, NCB means no claim
bonus, if you do not take this, then 10 percent no
claim bonus is charged on top of it, if you do
not subscribe, then due to its
change every 5 years, the
premium also changes when the age increases
from 40 years to 60 years, this means that the
premium in this category is PIMPLE
because FD
comes, so these were some details of both the
super top loops.  Regarding comparison, it
is very important for us to get good coverage for ourselves, so you
can select any of these two companies on Super Top,
both are very good,
we keep bringing information about subscription, so please
like and subscribe to our channel,
thank you for watching.